pegasusnews.com 2007-12-29

# Privacy Policy | pegasusnews.com | Dallas / Fort Worth

**About PegasusNews.com**   
PegasusNews.com (the “Website”) is an online service operated by Pegasus News, Inc., a Texas corporation (“Pegasus News”). If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at [privacy@pegasusnews.com](mailto:privacy@pegasusnews.com). 

**Information Collection and Use by Pegasus News**   
Pegasus News gathers identifying information about individuals only when individuals provide that information on a voluntary basis pursuant to the voluntary registration process for the Website.  Such information includes, but is not limited to, name, age, gender, email address, cell phone number, personal interests, and physical address.  We use this voluntary profile data to (a) provide customized content to users, (b) authenticate users, (c) send notifications to users relating to the Website, (d) assist users in communicating with each other, and (e) make offers to users that we believe may be of interest to them based on their personal profile data.  With the exception of email address, physical address and cell phone number, registered users’ voluntary personal profile information, including pictures, are displayed to other registered users in order to facilitate user interaction.  Registered users’ user names are displayed to all users, although each verified user has the option of having his or her full name displayed to all users instead of his or her user name.  Under no circumstances are email addresses, physical addresses and cell phone numbers directly revealed to other users or disclosed to third parties other than as set forth below in the “Sharing and Disclosure of Information” section. 

Pegasus News logs information about use of the Website, including, but not limited to, IP address, profile information, pages visited, and browser type, from users of the Website.  This data is used for, among other things, to provide customized content to users, provide targeted offers to users, manage the site, track usage and improve the site services. 

Users must provide us, at a minimum, with a valid email address in order to complete the voluntary registration process.  Email addresses are used to send notifications related to the Website and to communicate offers. Registered users may choose not to receive promotional emails from us by changing the “Do not send me promotional emails” setting within their personal profile, although such users may still receive emails from us concerning non-promotional Website communications. Registered users may communicate with each other through the Website without disclosing their email addresses. 

Cell phone numbers are used to send text and voice message notifications related to the Website and to communicate offers. Registered users may choose not to receive text messages from us by not providing their cell phone number to us at registration. Registered users who have provided their cell phone number to us may remove it from within their personal profile settings.   

Pegasus News does not sell or make available any individual user information to unrelated third parties, except to third parties that are providing services to Pegasus News or as provided in the “Sharing and Disclosure of Information” section below.  We may aggregate user information for the purpose of user analyses and inform advertisers of the results of such analyses. In all such instances, Pegasus News will refer only to general, aggregate usage data from these analyses and will never provide specific identifying information. We may also aggregate user information for the purpose of making offers to users that we believe may be of interest to them. 

Third parties can read information voluntarily posted by registered users on the Website.  That information can be used by those third parties to send you unsolicited messages.  Pegasus News has no control over such unsolicited messages. 

**Use of Cookies **   
The Website uses cookies to store users’ preferences and to record session information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set.  Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.  However, you must enable cookies from www.PegasusNews.com in order to use most functions on the site.  Third party advertisers on the site may have the ability to set and access their cookies on your computer.  Advertisers’ use of cookies are subject to their own privacy policies and are not subject to this Privacy Policy. 

**Links**   
The Website contains links to other websites.  Pegasus News is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on the Website.  Furthermore, Pegasus News bears no responsibility for any offensive material or violations of law on any site linked from the Website. 

**Correcting/Updating Information and Terminating Registration **   
Registered users may modify any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing their personal profile. Registered users may terminate their registration at any time, for any reason, by contacting [customerservice@pegasusnews.com](mailto:customerservice@pegasusnews.com). 

**Third Party Advertising **   
Ads appearing on the Website may be delivered to users by Pegasus News or one of our advertising partners. Our advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Pegasus News and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp). 

**Security **   
Registered user accounts are secured by user-created passwords.  Pegasus News uses reasonable measures to protect registered user information that is stored within our database. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of registered user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of registered user information at any time. For any additional information about the security measures we use on the Website, please contact us at [privacy@pegasusnews.com](mailto:privacy@pegasusnews.com).  

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information **   
Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, Pegasus News will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (a) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by Pegasus News; (b) to enforce our [_Terms of Use Agreement_](http://www.pegasusnews.com/about/pegasus/termsofuse/) or to protect our rights; or (c) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the Website. Pegasus News reserves the right to transfer, disclose or sell personal information as part of a business divestiture, sale, merger, or acquisition of Pegasus News or substantially all of its assets.  For more information see the “Changes in Our Privacy Policy” section below. 

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy **   
From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy.  If we make changes, we will post them on the Website to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A user is bound by any changes to the policy when she or he uses the Website after those changes have been posted.  If, however, we intend to disclose users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will post a notice of such intent on the Website 30 days prior to such action. 

**Contacting Us **   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of the Website, or your dealings with the Website, please contact us at: [privacy@pegasusnews.com](mailto:privacy@pegasusnews.com) (8140 Walnut Hill Lane, Suite 605, Dallas, Texas 75231). 

**Effective Date**   
This privacy policy is effective as of December 1, 2006. It was last updated on November 1, 2007.
